我们昨晚在铁板烧店碰见你妈了
Oh, hey, we ran into your mom at Benihana last night.
是啊  她超爱去那里
Uh, yeah, she loves that place.
每次大厨把大虾翻炒到空中时
Every time they flip a shrimp in the air,
她会一个飞扑上去叼住
she practically leaps out of her seat to catch it.
所以我从不带她去海洋公园[喂海豚]
That's why I don't take her to the Seaworld.
我知道你不想听到这事
I know you don't want to hear it,
但是她是跟斯图尔特一起去的
but she was there with Stuart.
随便啊  我又无所谓
That's fine. I don't care.
他们出去约会你不会不爽吗
It doesn't bug you when they go out on dates?
他们不是约会
They're not dating.
只是两个朋友一起出去吃饭
They're just two friends who went out to dinner.
吃完一起回他们共住的房子
And then went back to the home they share
没准睡觉时两人还穿着
where they probably fell asleep
你妈妈买的情侣睡衣
in the matching pajamas she got them
因为他们俩都喜欢企鹅
because they both just love penguins.
很多不是情侣的人也穿着情侣睡衣啊
Hey, lots of people wear matching pajamas who aren't dating.
比如说
Like who?
你和你的狗
Like you and your dog.
话别说太早哦
Don't rule out the dating.
行  我心里超不爽
Fine, it bothers me.
你们高兴了吧
You happy?
你这问题算什么啊
You think you've got problems.
长臂猿是人猿总科中
The gibbon is the only member of the ape family
唯一不是大猿的猿类
not classified as a great ape.
你这话对我有啥帮助
How is this helpful?
所有非人类的猩猩
All the non-human apes are classified
全都归在人猿总科下的人科里
as great apes except one.
这就表示
That means
分类学家创造了小猿这个分类
taxonomists created the entire category of lesser ape
来孤立可怜的长臂猿
just to single out the poor gibbon
他就像操场上被排挤的小孩
as the weird kid on the playground.
这些毛茸茸的小伙心中才是真不爽呢
Now there's a hairy little fellow with a genuine beef.
但是长臂猿们不知道自己被分类成什么
But the gibbon doesn't know what it's categorized as.
它们都不知道自己叫长臂猿
It doesn't even know it's called a gibbon.
这倒是
True.
抱歉  兄台  你比长臂猿还惨
Sorry, kid, you've got it worse than a gibbon.
电影之夜我们带零食来了
We brought snacks for movie night.
太好了
Oh, great.
你们不会顺便还带了餐巾纸  干净的碗
I don't suppose you also brought napkins, clean bowls,
餐具外加一卷厕纸吧
utensils and a roll of toilet paper.
还真带了
Right here.
你们最好了
You guys are the best.
这些衣服是怎么回事
What's with the clothes?
我为了工作买了不少职业装
Well, with all the new stuff I bought for work,
衣橱得清出一些空位啊
I needed to make room in my closet.
我是问这次衣服怎么是叠好的
I meant why are they folded?
不过随便吧
But whatever.
这件是干嘛的
Ooh, what's this?
说了怕你们不信  那是我当年的毕业舞会裙
That, believe it or not, is my prom dress.
你还留着啊
Wow, you still have it?
我还以为会急忙中被揉成一团
I just assumed it was balled up
丢到谷仓的某个角落去了
in the corner of a barn somewhere.
你把我当年想成是哪种人了啊
What kind of teenager did you think I was?
-淫荡  -风骚
- Slutty. - Easy.
那是叫"受欢迎"好吗
The word is "popular."
你当年的舞会如何  你去了吗
How was your prom? Did you go?
没  但我去打扫了
No, but I was on clean-up crew.
太可怜了
Aw, that's sad.
不会  其实也还行
No, it was okay.
DJ在收工前  让我与我的拖把
The DJ let me dance one slow song with my mop
共舞了一曲慢歌
before he shut down.
每当我看到一桶脏水
Whenever I see a bucket of dirty water,
耳边还会响起那曲《红衣女郎》
I still hear "Lady in Red."
我当年的舞会也挺糟糕
My prom was pretty terrible, too.
当时我超兴奋那个男生来约我
I was so excited about my date,
结果发现他是为了泡我朋友
but it turned out he only asked me
所以才来约我
'cause he liked my friend.
他一整个晚上都在聊我的朋友
He spent the whole night talking about her.
行行行  你有朋友又有人约
Okay, we get it, you had a friend and a date.
少显摆了好吗
Stop bragging.
无所谓啦
Doesn't matter.
毕业舞会蠢爆了
Prom is silly anyways.
你说当然容易
Easy for you to say;
你当年估计是跟橄榄球队队长一起去的
you probably went with the captain of the football team.
才不是
No.
我只是趁他的舞伴喝吐时
I just made out with him a little
偷偷跟他亲热了一番
while his date was puking.
那呕吐物就会是我的舞伴拖把来清理
My date would've had to clean that up.
我有个主意
Ooh, I have an idea.
我们可以来一个二次舞会啊
Maybe we can have, like, a prom do-over.
那应该会很好玩吧
Oh, that would be so much fun.
我们可以布置一下屋顶  让他们穿晚礼服
We could decorate the roof and make the guys wear tuxedos.
我们也去弄好头发  然后与他们跳慢舞
Ooh, and get our hair done, and slow-dance.
两位  相信我
Okay, guys, trust me,
作为去过大概有七场毕业舞会的人
as someone who's been to, like, seven proms,
舞会永远不会如你们想象中那般美好
it is never as good as you want it to be.
你去了七场舞会吗
You went to seven proms?
对  我想想
Yeah, let's see.
四场"深海主题"  两场"魔法奇缘"
Uh, four "Under the Seas," Two "Enchanted Evenings,"
一场"难忘之夜"
and one "Night to Remember"
那一夜我可是喝到一点都记不得
that... I cannot remember for the life of me.
伯纳黛特呢
Hey, where's Bernadette?
她跟艾米出去买舞会的礼服了
She and Amy are out dress shopping for their prom thing.
我有收到电邮邀请
Oh, yeah, I got that Evite.
我看完《红粉佳人》后
Ever since I saw Pretty in Pink,
1986年青春爱情校园电影
片中有毕业舞会桥段
我也好想参加美国人的毕业舞会
I've wanted to go to an American prom.
但看完《魔女嘉丽》
But then I saw Carrie,
惊悚电影  有1976与2013两个版本  片中女主角在舞会上展开了一场大屠杀
我又一点都不想参加美国的毕业舞会了
and I did not want to go to an American prom.
但我又看了《一吻定江山》
But then I saw Never Been Kissed,
1990年浪漫喜剧电影  也有浪漫舞会桥段
我又重新想参加毕业舞会了
and I'm back on the prom bandwagon.
毕业舞会这事真让我的心大起大落啊
This prom thing's been a real roller coaster.
妮妮很兴奋呢
Bernie's really excited.
我知道她兴奋是因为她声音变超尖
I-I could tell because her voice got so high,
隔壁的狗听到都开始狗嚎了
the beagle next door started howling.
高音容易使狗开始嚎叫
你有去毕业舞会吗
Did you go to your prom?
没
No.
因为我与当个好学生有个约会
I had a date with a proper education.
比起一身燕尾服  我养成一身好习惯
Instead of a tuxedo, I dressed myself in good habits.
比起掺了烈酒的潘趣酒
Instead of spiked punch,
含酒精度较低的饮料酒
我更喜欢知识醉人的味道
I enjoyed the intoxicating flavor of knowledge.
比起在体育馆里跳舞
Instead of dancing in a gym,
我更愿意随着AP微积分诱人的节奏
I shook my booty to the seductive rhythms...
够了够了
Okay, okay.
...抖屁股
...of AP Calculus.
你怎么没有跟艾米和伯纳黛特一起去采购呢
How come you're not shopping with Amy and Bernadette?
我来猜猜  你觉得这个舞会主意烂爆了
Let me guess, you think the whole idea is lame?
不要管我怎么想  你觉得如何
Well, who cares what I think? What do you think?
老实说
Hmm, to be honest,
即使这是个假的毕业舞会  但能有你这么美的舞伴
it's kind of a dream come true to go to even a fake prom
也算是美梦成真吧
with a woman as beautiful as you.
真是谢谢了
Ugh, thanks a lot.
怎么了
What?
要是我说不想参加  不就成了坏女人了吗
Well, now I can't blow this thing off without being a bitch.
所以说她答应了
That sounds like a "Yes"!
每一位受邀的人都回复说参加
Ooh, every single person RSVP'd "Yes."
真是太让人激动了
This is so exciting!
你说是不是呀
Isn't this exciting?
是
Yep.
就连斯尔图特都要带舞伴来
Look, even Stuart's bringing a date.
真好奇那人是谁
I wonder who it is.
你明明知道那人是谁
You know exactly who it is.
我妈就是他的舞伴
He's gonna bring my mom.
你干嘛要邀请他啊
Why did you even invite him?
因为他是我们的朋友  你们俩必须和睦相处
Because he's our friend, and you two need to get along.
再说了  他为什么不能带你妈来
And why can't he take your mom?
你毕业舞会的时候不也带了吗
You took her to your prom.
我没有"带"她去  她是去"监护"我
I didn't "Take" her; she was a chaperone.
我见过一张你们一起跳舞的照片
I saw a picture of you two dancing together.
不能怪我
W-What was I gonna do?
当时在播我们爱的主打歌
They were playing our song!
我受不了了
I can't take this anymore.
你好
Hello.
斯尔图特  我们得谈谈
Stuart, we have to talk.
你跟我妈那点事儿
This thing with you and my mom,
让我超不爽
I-I hate it.
都快把我逼疯了
It's making me crazy.
你我是多年的朋友了
You and I were friends for years,
如今你却要带我妈去参加
and now you're bringing my mother to a party
我也在场的舞会
I'm going to?!
太离谱了吧
What the hell?!
我没有要带你妈去啊  我有其他舞伴
I'm not bringing your mother, I have a date.
所以你现在是背着我妈偷吃吗
Oh, so now you're cheating on my mother?
你在胡说什么呀
Wha-What are you talking about?
我和你妈之前完全不存在任何逾越之举
There's nothing weird going on with me and your mother.
图仔  你的洗澡水要凉了哦
Stewie, your bath is getting cold!
我得挂了  再见
I got to go, bye.
佩妮
Penny?
Penny.
佩妮
今天敲门的次数比平时多呀
You knocked more than usual.
下次我可能有急事
Next time I might be in a rush,
先多敲两下存着吧
it's good to have a few in the bank.
找我干嘛
Okay, what's up?
我想跟你讨论下
I'd like to discuss this party
艾米和伯纳黛特举办的这个舞会
that Amy and Bernadette are throwing.
既然我和你都不想参加
Since you and I are both reluctant to go,
我想到了一个让我们乐在其中的完美方法
I think I've come up with a perfect way for us to enjoy it.
好呀  怎么做
Great, how?
假装我们是外星人
We pretend we're aliens.
我不擅长阅读面部表情
I'm not the best at reading facial cues,
但我猜你很喜欢这主意  并想深入了解它
but I'm gonna say that you love it and want to hear more.
在受人喜爱的小说
Now, in the beloved novel
《银河系漫游指南》中
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy,
一位叫福特・派法特的外星人为了混进人类世界
an alien named Ford Prefect pretended to be human
假扮人类
in order to blend in
目的就是为替《银河系漫游指南》
so that he could write an entry about Earth
写一本地球指南
for The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy,
而这本旅游指南恰恰是一本真书的一部分
which is a travel book within the actual book,
而那本真书名字就叫
which is also called
《银河系漫游指南》
The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
我只有一个问题
Okay, just one question.
你说什么
What?
我的意思是  假装外星人
My point is, pretending to be an alien is
是我使用过多次非常有用的应对机制
a valuable coping mechanism I've used many times.
我第一次去看你演出时就用过
I did it the first time I went to see you in a play.
你根本不知道观众里有
You had no idea Commander Umfrumf
来自天镄堑闹富庸
of Ceti Alpha Three was in the audience.
别担心  他竖起七根大拇指叫好哦
Oh, d-don't worry, he gave you seven thumbs up.
那么问题来了
Here's a question--
作为假扮人类的外星人
as an alien pretending to be human,
你打算跟艾米遵循
are you planning to engage in any
舞会后人类交配的惯例吗
post-prom mating rituals with Amy?
舞会后还有交配的惯例吗
There are post-prom mating rituals?
也不尽然啦
Not always.
但如果你舞伴的货车上有充气床垫
Unless your date drives a van with an air mattress,
那就是惯例啦
then always.
如果这是舞会体验的一部分  那我愿意接受
Well, if it's part of the prom experience, then I'm open to it.
你开玩笑呢吧
You're kidding.
我或许是个外星人  但我也有冲动啊
I may be an alien, but I have urges.
如果艾米想交配  把卵子发射进太空
If Amy wants to copulate by firing her eggs into space,
那好  我很乐意用
well, then, I will happily catch them
我"上殖器"的生殖囊兜住它们
with the reproductive sac on my upper flermin.
虽然我不擅长阅读面部表情
I'm not the best at reading facial cues,
但我能看出你有点小性奋哦
but I can see that you're a little turned on.
如果你懒得学怎么系领结
You know, if you're not gonna learn how to do this,
有很多夹上去的领结也很漂亮
they make some pretty good clip-ons.
布鲁斯・韦恩[蝙蝠侠]才不用夹上去的领结
Bruce Wayne doesn't wear a clip-on.
布鲁斯・韦恩也不会让他的室友帮忙系啊
Bruce Wayne doesn't make his roommate tie it for him.
他的室友[管家]阿福  会帮他系领带啊
His name is Alfred, and, yes, he does.
好了  完美
There, perfect.
你确定吗
What, are you sure?
这是我人生第一场毕业舞会  我可得按照规矩来
It's my first prom, I want to do it correctly.
我以为你要打破常规扮外星人呢
I thought you were gonna pretend to be an alien.
我想来着  不过佩妮不想
I was, but Penny didn't want to.
你也不想
You didn't want to.
伯纳黛特  艾米
Bernadette, Amy,
库萨帕里和沃罗威茨都不想
Koothrappali and Wolowitz didn't want to.
而连我都知道  请临演来会很怪
And even I knew it was weird to hire somebody.
那是酒壶吗
Was that a flask?
是的
Yes.
我决定接受所有和舞会
I've decided to embrace all of the traditions
相关的传统  包括在潘趣酒里掺烈酒
associated with prom, including spiking the punch.
你要在潘趣酒里掺烈酒
You're gonna put alcohol in the punch?
才不  这是石榴汁
Oh, no, this is pomegranate juice.
用保护细胞老化的抗氧化物
It's all the fun of high school high jinks
来玩高中生寻欢作乐的游戏
with the cell-protecting zip of antioxidants.
如果你再穿上破烂的牛仔裤和皮夹克
If you had ripped jeans and a leather jacket,
你就可以当迪士尼儿童台中的校霸了
you'd be like the toughest kid on the Disney Channel.
今晚还有什么安排吗
So, anything else planned for tonight?
舞会一切要做的事
Oh, everything.
跟大家照相  慢舞
Getting our picture taken, slow-dancing,
被选为舞会国王
being elected prom king.
再指正大家国王不是民选的
Pointing out that kings aren't elected.
到时候肯定爽翻天
It's gonna be off the hook.
既然你提起了
And while you're at it,
我知道在这个年龄你的荷尔蒙激增
I know that at this age your hormones are raging,
虽然你的朋友们都在嘿咻
but just because all your friends are having sex
不见得你也非得去做
doesn't mean you have to.
你何出此言
Why would you say that?
因为...
You know, 'cause...
很多人的初夜都是在毕业舞会上失去的
'cause a lot of people lose their virginity on prom night.
佩妮也暗示过这个
Penny implied the same thing.
是真的吗
Is this true?
放轻松  我开玩笑的
Just relax, it's a joke.
你根本没有荷尔蒙
You don't have hormones.
你真漂亮
Wow, you look amazing.
谢谢  你也很帅
Thank you, so do you.
谢尔顿  你真帅气
Sheldon, you look so handsome.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢尔顿  艾米不漂亮吗
Sheldon, doesn't Amy look hot?
是不是让你的"上殖器"都活跃起来啦
That's got to put some starch in the upper flermin.
什么东西
What's that?
那是长在他肩胛骨之间的
Oh, it's a scaly genital organ
鳞状生殖器
that grows between his shoulder blades.
跳舞的时候小心别碰着了
Try not to touch it when you're dancing.
失陪了
Excuse me.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我做不到
I can't do this.
莱纳德  我告诉你
And for your information, Leonard,
"上殖器"不是长在我的肩胛骨之间
the upper flermin doesn't grow between my shoulder blades,
而是从我脖子的肚脐孔上长出来的
it grows out of the belly button on my neck.
他说得对  我刚才说成"下殖器"了
He's right, I was thinking of the lower flermin.
我给斯图尔特发短信  说我们快到了
Ooh, I'll, uh, text Stuart, let him know we're close.
你的纹身真好看
That's a neat tattoo.
谢谢  这是《圣诞夜惊魂》里的萨利
Oh, thanks, it's Sally from Nightmare before Christmas.
那部电影很有趣
Aw, that movie's so cute.
你喜欢她  是因为你们都是红头发吗
Do you like her because you both have red hair?
不尽然  更多是因为她浑身伤疤
Uh, a little, but more that she's covered in scars
还可以把四肢都拆下来  然后重新缝上
and can pull her own limbs off and sew them back on.
我喜欢《灰姑娘》
I like Cinderella.
你知道在《灰姑娘》原书中
Did you know, in the original book,
灰姑娘的姐姐们为了能穿进水晶鞋
the sisters cut off their toes with knives
用刀把脚趾头砍了下来吗
in order to fit in the glass slipper?
我喜欢《魔咒歌》
I like "Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo."
迪士尼动画电影《灰姑娘》中的歌曲
斯图尔特和他的女伴来了
Hey, here comes Stuart and his date.
她真可爱
Oh, she's cute.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What?
那人是珍妮
That's Jeanie.
她就是珍妮吗
That's Jeanie?!
-珍妮是谁  -别说
- Who's Jeanie? - Don't say it.
霍华德以前睡过的那个堂姐
That's Howard's cousin that he had sex with.
她是我的二等堂姐
She is my second cousin.
我们当时只有15岁  我叫你别说
We were 15... I just said, "don't say it."
没关系
No, it's okay.
他很早以前就告诉我了
He told me that story a long time ago.
拉杰
Raj!
那是我们第一次约会
It was our first date,
突然冷场了
there was an awkward silence.
我总得找话题说啊
What was I supposed to say?
好漂亮啊
Oh, it's beautiful.
她们俩布置得真漂亮
Oh, the girls really did a nice job.
我之前虽然不太感兴趣
I know I wasn't into this before,
不过我很高兴能带你来你的第一个舞会
but I'm so glad I get to take you to your first prom.
你为什么觉得我没参加毕业舞会
What makes you think I didn't go to my prom?
-我去了  -你带了谁
- I went. - Well, who'd you go with?
我带的女伴名叫"孤独"
I took a little lady I like to call loneliness.
没事啦
Aw, it's all right.
我们最后和"丢脸"
We ended up having a threesome
来了个"三人大战"
with her friend humiliation, so...
如果我当时在场  看见你一个人
Well, if I would have been there and saw you alone,
我一定会邀请你跳舞
I would've asked you to dance.
不  你不会的
No, you wouldn't have.
你怎么知道
Well, you don't know that.
那时候我还没发育呢
It was before my growth spurt.
什么  你现在是发育过了吗
What, that already happened?
真好笑
Very funny.
不过你肯定也不会邀请我
Well, you wouldn't have asked me either.
我肯定会邀请你
I would have asked you.
在我脑子里
In my head.
在回家的路上
On the way home.
大哭的时候邀请你
While I was having a good cry.
谢尔顿  我能进来吗
Sheldon, can I come in?
我觉得还是算了吧
I don't think that's a good idea.
为什么
Why not?
根据网上的留言板说
According to an online message board,
我可能是恐慌症犯了
I may be having a panic attack.
"足球妈妈09"也有同样的症状
SoccerMom09 had similar symptoms.
不过说实话  她的双胞胎那天的确很不乖
But to be fair, the twins were a real handful that day.
你让我很担心
You're making me worry.
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
事情是我们要去参加毕业舞会
What's going on is we're about to go to a prom.
对我们这样的青年情侣来说
And there's a great deal of pressure
要做到鲍勃・尤班克斯
on young couples like us to engage in
美国新婚游戏节目主持人
说的那样"肆意狂欢"  有很大压力
what Mr. Bob Eubanks called making whoopee.
什么压力
What pressure?
我不过就说了你好帅
All I said was you look handsome.
把门打开好吗
Can you please open the door?
不光是这样
It's not just that.
莱纳德和佩妮也说了这事
Leonard and Penny also made comments about it.
我又不是瞎子
And I'm not blind.
我都忍不住多看两眼我的翘臀
Even I looked twice when I saw my posterior
裹在礼服裤里的样子
in these tuxedo pants.
我跟珍妮相识于你阿姨格拉蒂家
So, I met Jeanie at your Aunt Gladys'.
她递给我犹太典礼酒
She passed me the Manischewitz,
我看了这犹太美女一眼
I took one look at this punim,
差点犹太式"喷"到犹太布丁上
and I almost plotzed on the kugel.
我谈论印度时也这么烦人吗
Is this what I sound like when I talk about India?
我妈对此没意见吗
So, my mother's okay with this?
你妈干嘛对我和斯图尔特有意见
Why would your mother have a problem with me and Stuart?
因为他们之间存在着不恰当的逾越之举
'Cause they have a weird, inappropriate relationship.
比咱俩在我爸车里"做"的事还逾越吗
Weirder than what you and I did in my dad's Corolla?
真是太"糟糕"了
This is so messed up.
我知道  我看得好开心啊
I know, I'm having the best time.
你今天为什么要来
Why would you even come to this?
你不是知道我也会在场吗
Didn't you know I'd be here?
那事都过去多久了  霍华德
It was a long time ago, Howard.
而且你俩是二等堂姐弟  有啥关系
And you're only second cousins, who cares?
珍妮与霍华德关系为同房远堂  也就是外国人眼中二等堂(second cousin)
你明知道这事还非要带她来吗
So, you knew and you brought her anyway?
霍德华能上她  我却不能上吗
Oh, so she's good enough for Howard, but not for me?!
没错
Yeah.
滚回家和你自己妈妈
Yeah, go have weird relationships
堂姐玩不伦去吧
with your own mother and cousin.
这是他的地盘
This is his turf.
说得对
Yeah.
我之前没请你跳舞
Well, I might not have asked you to dance then,
-现在让我邀请你吧  -可是没音乐啊
- but I will ask you now. - There's no music.
我不管
I don't care.
咱们自己制造音乐嘛
We'll make our own music.
瞧瞧  现在谁像个傻瓜啊
My God, who's the dork now?
谢谢你穿了平跟鞋
Thank you for wearing your flats.
谢谢你穿了高跟鞋
Thank you for wearing your heels.
看我多有出息
Look at me.
和舞会中最美的姑娘一起跳舞
Dancing with the prettiest girl at the prom.
想不想拍张合影发给
Want to take a picture of us and send it
你象棋俱乐部的朋友啊
to your old friends in the chess club?
我几年前就把你的泳装照发给他们了
I sent them a bikini shot of you years ago.
这样真好
This is nice.
我都有点希望其他人不来了
I kind of wish no one else was coming.
我也这么想
I know, me, too.
但能过个不混乱的毕业舞会也不错
But it will be fun to have a prom without all the drama.
华仔  放开他
Howie, get off of him!
除非这只猪不再专拱我家的白菜
Not until he stops humping his way up my family tree!
谢尔顿  你太傻了
Sheldon, this is silly.
我不要又错过一次舞会
I'm not missing another prom.
我要上楼去了
I'm going upstairs now.
回见
Good-bye.
我真心觉得你今天很美
I really did think you looked pretty.
真的吗
You did?
真的
Yes.
惊艳到让我开始恐慌
So much so that I started to panic.
你不用紧张
Well, you can relax.
就算你觉得我很美
Just because you think I look pretty
也不代表我们今晚就要在一起
doesn't mean we have to spend the night together.
可这是舞会  你不就想这样吗
Were you hoping we would because it's prom?
我一直都想
I'm always hoping.
但今晚我只想好好和你享受舞会
But tonight I just wanted to have a nice time with you.
或许还能跟有手臂的生物跳舞
And maybe dance with someone who has arms.
谢谢你理解我
Thank you for understanding.
我当然理解
Of course I understand.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
有些话我一直想告诉你
there's something else I've been wanting to say,
在说之前  我...
but before I do, I just...
我想让你明白  你不用回复我
I want you to know that you don't have to say it back.
我知道你还没准备好
I know you're not ready,
所以我不希望你
and I don't want you to say it
仅仅因为社交规矩而说出来
just because social convention dictates...
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你说出来了
You said it.
我对你有着不可否认
There's no denying I have feelings for you
又无法用其他途径解释的好感
that can't be explained in any other way.
我曾以为自己脑子里长了寄生虫
I briefly considered that I had a brain parasite.
但那个理由更牵强
But that seems even more farfetched.
唯一的结论  这就是爱
The only conclusion was love.
我知道你怎么了
I know what's happening.
你这是恐慌发作
This is a panic attack.
"足球妈妈09"说要双腿抬高马上躺下
SoccerMom09 says to lie down with your feet elevated.
好的
Okay.
虽然我说了我爱你
Just because I love you doesn't mean
但不代表女生可以进我房间啊
girls are allowed in my room.
好了
Okay.
照相啦
Here we go...
说"茄子"
Say "Cheese"!
说"田七"
说"堂姐"
Say "Cousin"!
说
Say...
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
等一下  抱歉
Hang on, sorry.
黛比
Hey, Debbie.
我...是的  我和珍妮在一起
I... Yeah, yeah, I'm here with Jeanie.
可我和她只是朋友
Okay, but we're just friends.
只是...  好吧
It's... Yeah.
我得赶紧走了
I got to go.